{"data":[{"question":"As we have finished the first lesson, now we will read the second one.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"look ","b":"like ","c":"mistaken for ","d":"each other","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Like-> similar","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Why is a man in civil life perpetually slandering and backbiting his fellow men, and is unable to see good even in his friends?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As ","b":"other ","c":"used to define ","d":"its ","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- As->like","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Like a synonym of speech, which is the general term, address implies some degree of formality.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"conviction ","b":"likely ","c":"result in ","d":"resigns","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Resigns-> resigned","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Rabbits and hares look much like and are often mistaken for each other.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are made of ","b":"which ","c":"they ","d":"are called ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Which-> where","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"As every other nation, the United States used to define its unit of currency, the dollars, in terms of the gold standard.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"trips ","b":"between ","c":"painted","d":"on ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Paited-> paint","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The prime minister's conviction for improper campaign practices is likely to result in increasing pressure that she resigns.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was settled ","b":"a hilly","c":"the ","d":"harbors","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Harbors-> harbor","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"When the boulders are made of rock that is different from the bedrock which they or the soil of the field rests, they are called erratics.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"returned ","b":"her native New York","c":"art revolutionary ","d":"day","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Art revolutionary-> art revolution","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"After his trips to the west between 1860 and 1872, Ralph Alber Bakelock would often painted American Indian encampments on brown-and-yellow-toned canvases.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"became ","b":"member permanent ","c":"of the ","d":"in ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Member permanent-> permanent member","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The city of Boston was settled in 1630 on a hilly, wooded peninsula where the charles River flows into a natural harbors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is thought to ","b":"does not ","c":"considering ","d":"species","answer":"1","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Contralto Marian Anderson became a member permanent of the Metropolitan Opera Company in 1995.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"recording ","b":"vary ","c":"branches ","d":"are ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Vary-> various","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}